http://www.terrylabs.com/terms-and-privacy.html

Menu
TERRY LABORATORIES, L.L.C.
Privacy Policy / Website Terms and Conditions
OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND SECURITY PLEDGE:
Thank you for visiting terrylabs.com!
This policy addresses the personal information we collect, how we use it and how we protect it. Your satisfaction with this website is important to us. Assuring the privacy and security of all of the information you share with us on this website is an important part of that satisfaction. We want to be open and clear with regard to how we handle your personal information. Please find our policies listed below.
1. Collection and Use of Personal Information
1.1 Terry Laboratories, L.L.C.,(hereinafter referred to as “Terry Labs”), takes great pride in adhering to all applicable federal and state laws and will not share your personal information with any outside companies or vendors except for the facilitation of a business related process or financial transactions on your behalf.
1.2 Personal information is deemed to include the following:
Name
Address
Phone Number
E-mail Address
Credit Card Information
2. Protecting Your Information
2.1 Terry Labs uses a secure server.The secure server software (SSL) encrypts ALL of the information you provide to us, including your name, address and phone number, before it is sent to us so that it cannot be read as it travels to us over the internet. Once we receive it, all of the customer information we collect is protected against unauthorized access. We do this by following these following steps:
2.1.1 Firewall – Terry Lab’s systems are protected 24 hours a day by a powerful firewall that blocks unauthorized entry. In order to gain access to authorized information, the Web browser you are using must know the proper protocol, or language.
2.1.2 Encryption – From the moment information leaves your computer to the time is enters our systems, all online access is encrypted.
We employ some of the strongest forms of encryption commercially available for use on the Web today. During any transfer of data, our 128-bit encryption turns your information into a coded sequence with billions of possible variations, making it nearly impossible for unwanted intruders to decipher.
2.13 Employee access – We limit employee access to customer information to those who have a business
reason to know this information.
2.2 Although we intend to take all reasonable steps to prevent the introduction of viruses and other destructive materials or hackers, we cannot and do not
guarantee or warrant that this website, or materials that may be downloaded from this website, do not contain such destructive features. We are not liable for any damages or harm attributable to any of the foregoing.
2.3 Terry Lab’s does not share your personal information with any outside companies or vendors. In the event you do not want to provide any
personal information over the internet? No problem, just call our customer service center at 321 259-1630 or email us at Aloe@terrylabs.com
3. Legal Terms and Conditions/Disclaimer
You’re Consent. By accessing or using this web site, you agree to accept and comply with the
terms, conditions, notices and disclaimers contained herein and elsewhere on
the web site (known collectively as “Terms and Conditions”), and you consent to the collection and use of the data you provide to Terry Labs.
3.2 Use of “Cookies”. A cookie is a small text file used to identify you. Cookies sometimes receive an undeserved negative reputation because they are used to identify website visitors, when in fact, cookies are safe in that: (a) they cannot deliver computer viruses to your computer; (b) other computer servers
cannot read them; and (c) personal information cannot be obtained by other computers. Cookies tell us that it is
you whenever you return to our website so that we can recall what information you have provided to us in terms of what you like and want to do on our
website. We use cookies to personalize your website visits. Cookies are simply a unique identifier shared between you and us and we do not share them with anyone else.
3.3 Sharing Information with Third Parties. Terry Labs does not sell, trade, or rent any information you provide to any unrelated
third party. We do not share customer information with outside parties who may wish to market their products to you. There are other situations when we may disclose to third parties the customer information we collect as permitted by law. Third parties could include
government entities, courts, or other entities (in response to a subpoenas and other legal processes), and those with whom you have requested us to share
information.
3.4 Links to other Websites. This website may contain links to other third party websites to provide
our guests with additional information that may make your visit to our website
more beneficial. All of these websites
are owned and operated independently of Terry Labs. Each has their own separate privacy and data collection policies. Terry Labs has no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the independent actions or policies of these independent websites and is not responsible for the content or practices of such third-party websites.
3.5 Opting-Out of E-Mails.  Terry Labs may collect email addresses at various points on the website. Our intention is that you should only receive email
communications that will be useful to you and that you want to receive, so we
provide you the ability to unsubscribe or opt-out from all marketing
communications, offers and promotions and surveys.  Providing your email address in most areas on the website may be optional. If at any time you wish to stop receiving any promotional email messages from us, simply follow the instructions in relation to “opting
out” of future emails in any email you receive from us.
3.6 Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability. This website is provided on an “as is” basis. Terry Labs does not
make any warranties, express or implied, including without limitation, warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, compatibility, security, correctness, completeness, usefulness, or non-infringement with respect to this website or any information provided on this website. You assume full responsibility and risk of loss, including loss of data, resulting from your use of this web site. While we intend to take all reasonable steps to prevent the introduction of viruses and other harmful material, we do not
warrant that this web site is free of viruses or other potentially harmful components. We do not warrant that this
website will be uninterrupted or error-free, and there may be delays, omissions, interruptions and inaccuracies in the content or other materials or goods available on this website. We do not accept responsibility for any error, omission or defect in the information.
3.7 Release.  You agree that Terry Labs (including without limitation its officers, directors, employees, and affiliated entities) will not be held liable for any claims, damages or costs, whether direct or indirect, consequential or special, arising out of or in any way connected to your use or inability to use this website or any hyperlinked website, or any information or goods that are purchased, if any, using this website, including lost profits, business interruption, loss of programs or other data, or otherwise. In addition, you agree that we may not be held liable for the conduct of other members associated with this website, including, but not limited to, activities relating to message boards or chat rooms, or any other services that may be offered in the future. You hereby waive any claims, whether based on contractual, tort or other grounds, even if we have been advised of the possibility of such damages. Some jurisdictions do not allow for limited liability or exclusion of implied warranties, therefore not all of the above limitations may apply to you.
3.8 Indemnity.  You agree to indemnify Terry Labs (including,
without limitation, their officers, directors, and employees) against any and
all claims and expenses, including attorney’s fees, arising out of or in any
way connected to your use of this website.
This expressly includes, without limitation, liability arising from your
violation or infringement of any rights of others, including their personal
information and any intellectual property rights.
3.9 Contact
Information. Terry Labs welcomes your feedback and any questions you may have about or Privacy Policy.  If you have any questions regarding the Terry
Lab’s Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at:  Terry Laboratories, L.L.C., 7005 Technology
Drive, Melbourne, FL 32904, Attention Customer Service or by email at:
California residents
may also contact: State of California, Department of Consumer Affairs, P.O. Box
942507, Sacramento, CA  94258-0507,
Telephone Number: 916-445-1254.
3.10 Copyright and Trademark Ownership. Terry Labs holds title, and ownership to all trademarks and content on the website.
Copyright © 2015 Terry Laboratories, L.L.C. All rights reserved.
3.11 Governing Law.  The terms and conditions of this policy shall
be governed in accordance with and pursuant to the laws of the State of Florida,
U.S.A.  Any action or proceeding that may
be brought arising out of, in connection with, or by reason of this policy,
Shall be governed by,
and construed in accordance with, the domestic laws of the State of Florida,
U.S.A., giving effect to the principles of conflicts of law thereof.
3.12 Severability. If any part of this Privacy Policy is held
invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect.
Changes to the Privacy Policy. Terry Labs reserves the right in its sole discretion to modify and amend its Privacy Policy at any time without notice, except as stated herein. Terry Labs will post any changes on this page so you are always aware of the terms and conditions of our current Privacy Policy pertaining to what data we collect and
how we may use it. You should check back periodically to review our Privacy Policy for any changes.
This Privacy Policy was last revised on August 5, 2015
Quick Links
Share On:
6 Reason To Choose Terry Labs Over Other Aloe Vera Manufacturers
Melbourne, FL 32904 U.S.A.
